Aryan Khandal

🕥 aryankhandal0 | 🛅 khandalaryan | 🔽 aryankhandal0@gmail.com | 📘 +91 9829244947

SUMMARY

Working as a Senior Full Stack Developer Developer @ Siemens Healthineers for the past 3.5 years, I have been developing and deploying Web Applications and REST APIs as microservices in C#, .NET (REST APIs), Angular with Azure Suite (DevOps, Kubernetes Services, SQL Server, etc.) and Agile Methodologies for improving healthcare.

SKILLS

Programming Languages Libraries, Tools & Frameworks C++, C#, Python, JS, TypeScript

.NET, Angular, Visual Studio, Microsoft Azure

Test Driven Development, Agile, Devops, SOLID, Design Principles

Work Experience

Senior Engineer - Design and Development

January 2022 - Present

Siemens Healthineers

Methodologies

- Developed RESTful web APIs in .NET Core that use Azure services for data storage, security, deployment, and monitoring.
- Create Docker images and publish them to Azure Container Registry and deploy these images using Kubernetes.
- Azure KeyVault, SQL Server and Azure File Share to store relational and non-relational data for the web API.
- Azure Log Analytics and App Insights to collect and analyze logs, metrics, and traces.
- YAML pipelines for build, release as well as other activities such as testing, nuget updates, etc.

Design and Development Engineer

August 2020 - December 2021

Siemens Healthineers

- Developed a scalable web application using Angular, HTML and CSS.
- Worked with Angular 13-16 to develop a web application with custom UI libraries
- Create Docker images and publish them to Azure Container Registry and deploy these images using Kubernetes

Research Engineer Internship

May 2019 - July 2019

ezDI, Inc. - Healthcare Data Intelligence

- Trained Language Models for Embeddings for Medical Data (ELMo) and worked with pretrained embeddings.
- Worked with Tensorflow(Keras), Python, MySQL, XML, AWS EC2.
- Improved ICD-10 Code Recommendation using ML
- Predicting E and M codes (Multi Class Text Classification Problem) with LSTM and Word2Vec.

Projects

Certificate Management Infrastructure - Medical Devices

- Application to maintain, and distribute publicly trusted certificates to medical devices
- Web Application for managament of device infrastructure by hospital admin
- Enabled with Authentication, Authorization and Monitoring
- Features such as Auto-Renewal, Revocation, etc.

Yes Bank Datathon

Github Link

- Ranked 1st among 50 teams including industry professionals and won 1st prize (Rs. 100,000) in Datathon.
- Predicted OHLCV for Stock Market using LSTM (Long Short Term Memory) as it retain important insights from the previous time steps and predictions is more accurate than using normal statistics.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020	Computer Science and Engg. (B.Tech.) at National Institute of Technology,	Hamirpur (GPA: 8.84/10)
2016	Class XII, CBSE (St. Anselm's Sr. Sec. School, Jaipur)	(93.2%)
2014	Class X, CBSE (St. Anselm's Sr. Sec. School, Jaipur)	(GPA: 9.2/10)